(Leonard:)it was kind of a spur
of the moment thing,
(Leonard:)and also, we don't like her.
(Penny:)Leonard, come on,
she's your mom.
(Penny:)If we can do something
to make her happy,
(Penny:)why wouldn't we?
(Leonard:)I just said why...
(Leonard:)we don't like her.
(Penny:)Hey, look,
then forget about her,
(Penny:)let's do it for us.
(Penny:)We could keep it
small and informal.
(Penny:)This time we can
invite our families.
(Leonard:)Is your brother out of prison?
(Penny:)Thanks to overcrowding, yeah.
(Leonard:)I'd love it
if my dad could come.
(Penny:)Oh, you have to invite him.
(Penny:)I haven't seen him
since the divorce.
(Leonard:)Oh, he's like a different man.
(Leonard:)Oh.
He stopped twitching,
(Leonard:)and I think he grew
an inch and a half.
(Penny:)Well, then it's settled.
(Penny:)Yay.
(Howard:)God.
(Penny:)So funny.
(Penny:)I never thought my second
marriage would be to you!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪